Guide to the Harry Weinberger Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Original accession, 1915-1943
  - Itzickson, Jacob
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, and miscellaneous papers concerning United States vs. Jacob Itzickson, 1919-1922. Itzickson was an editor of the magazine Freedom. The magazine had printed an editorial discouraging the purchase of liberty bonds and Itzickson was charged with obstructing a liberty loan drive. Weinberger arranged to have Itzickson deported to England at the defendant's own expense and the indictment was dismissed.
    - Correspondence
      - Abbott, Leonard D. (3), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Flynn, Elizabeth G.
        See: Workers' Defense Union, box 35, folder 9
      - Hoover, J. Edgar
        See: U.S. Department of Justice, box 35, folder 7
      - Itzickson, Jacob (37), 1919-1921 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Konoff, A. (3), 1919-1920 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Levine, Hilda (1), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Lowensohn, Mina (1), 1922 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - National Civil Liberties Bureau (2), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - U.S. Department of Justice (41), 1919-1922 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (32), 1920, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Workers' Defense Union (19), 1920-1922, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Legal papers, 1919-1920 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Jager, Henry
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes concerning New York vs. Henry Jager, 1917. Jager was charged with disorderly conduct tending to a breach of peace and sentenced to six months in the workhouse. Weinberger succeeded in having the sentence reduced to three months.
    - Correspondence
      - Grant, Percy S. (4), 1917 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Hammer, Julius (2), 1917 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Jager, Henry (14), 1917 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Legal papers, 1917 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Jankowitz, Max
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes concerning New York vs. Max Jankowitz, 1920. Jankowitz printed a book called The Sexual Question and was arrested on a charge of publishing obscene literature. With Weinberger acting as his attorney, Jankowitz stated that he had no more copies of the book and that no more would be published.
    - Correspondence
      - Jankowitz, Max (2), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - New York Society for the Supression of Vice (2), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Legal papers, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Jones, John A.
    The papers consist of letters and legal papers concerning John A. Jones vs. Elizabeth G. (Flynn) Jones, 1920. Weinberger was the attorney for Mrs. Jones in these divorce proceedings.
    - Correspondence
      - Davis, Philip R. (6), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Flynn, Elizabeth G. (2), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Legal papers, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Josephson, Aaron
    The papers consist of letters. Weinberger was consulted concerning the deportation of Josephson to Canada.
    - Joint Amnesty Committee (1), 1922 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Josephson, Aaron (2), 1922 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Stredwick, H. (1), 1922 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Kaplunoff, Matthew
    The papers consist of letters and legal papers. Kaplunoff was deemed an alien likely to become a public charge and held for deportation. Weinberger succeeded in having the deportation warrant cancelled.
    - Correspondence
      - DeSilver, Albert (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Flynn, Elizabeth G.
        See: Workers' Defense Union, box 35, folder 21
      - Hard, William (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Johnson, Albert (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Kaplan, Harry (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Kaplunoff, Matthew (4), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Knox, John C. (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - National Surety Company (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Pierce, Ralph S. (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (2), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Workers' Defense Union (9), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Legal papers, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Katzes, Arthur
    See: Bernstein, Ethel, box 11, folder 1
  - Klein, Joshua
    The papers consist of letters. Weinberger apparently investigated Klein's detention at Coombe's Sanitarium and deportation proceedings against him.
    - Klein, Joshua, 1919 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (3), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Kozlenko, William
    The papers consist of letters and legal papers. Weinberger represented Kozlenko in matters concerning the publication of Kozlenko's anthologies of plays.
    - Correspondence
      - Cane, Meville H. (9), 1940 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Dodd, Mead, and Co. (1), 1940 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Harcourt, Brace, and Co. (4), 1940 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Kozlenko, William (4), 1940 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Legal papers, 1939-1940 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Kramer, Louis
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, and miscellaneous papers concerning United States vs. Louis Kramer, Morris Becker, Louis Sternberg, and Joseph Walker and United States vs. Louis Kramer, 1917-1920. Weinberger was attorney for Kramer in these two cases. In the first case, Kramer was charged with interfering with the draft and sentenced to two years in the Atlanta Penitentiary. Kramer was charged in the second case with refusal to register under the Selective Service Act. Weinberger unsuccessfully appealed to the United States Supreme Court on the ground that the Act was unconstitutional. Upon his release from prison, Kramer was held for deportation because of his anarchistic activities. Weinberger, however, proved that Kramer was a citizen and deportation proceedings were dismissed.
    - Correspondence
      - C, G, H, K, N, S-U, W (25), 1917, 1919-1920, undated (Box 35, Folder 26)
      - American Civil Liberties Union (2), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Baldwin, Roger N. (2), 1919 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Castleton, Samuel M. (3), 1919-1920 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Cohen, Herbert (2), 1917 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Cohn, Michael A. (1), 1917 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - DeSilver, Albert
        See: American Civil Liberties Union, box 35, folder 27
      - Kovner, Hilda (1), 1920 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Kramer, Louis (86), 1917-1920 (Box 35, Folder 29-31)
      - New Jersey, Essex County Penitentiary (8), 1919-1920 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - O'Neill, Harry F. (5), 1917 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - People's Council of America (3), 1917 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - U.S. Department of Justice (20), 1917, 1919-1920 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (24), 1917, 1920-1921 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - U.S. Penitentiary, Atlanta, Georgia (4), 1919 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - U.S. Supreme Court, Clerk (6), 1917 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Legal papers, 1902, 1917 June-Sep, 1918, undated (Box 36, Folder 5-8)
  - Kreymborg, Alfred
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, clippings, and miscellaneous papers concerning Alfred Kreymborg vs. Jimmie Durante and the National Broadcasting Company, 1934-1935. Kreymborg, represented by Heinberger, sued Durante and NBC for Durante's unauthorized use of material from Kreymborg's Plays for Poet Mimes. The case was decided in favor of Durante on the grounds that the poems used were not dramatic works and thus not covered by the copyright. Weinberger appealed the decision and Durante settled out of court.
    - Correspondence
      - B, C, F, K, L, N, P, R, S, U (24), 1934-1936, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Authors' League of America (2), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Cane, Melville H. (4), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Clark, Barrett H. (2), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Durante, Jimmie (1), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Feldman, Gustave B. (7), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Geddes, Donald P. (2), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Greet, William C. (3), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Harcourt, Brace, and Co. (2), 1929 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Kreymborg, Alfred (65), 1934-1935 (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Library of Congress (10), 1929, 1934-1935 (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Powers, Mary (6), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Publishers' Weekly (4), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Sirovich, William I. (5), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Woolsey, John M. (2), 1934 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Legal papers
      - 1934 March-October (Box 36, Folder 16-20)
      - 1935 January (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
    - Notes (Box 37, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 37, Folder 6-7)
  - Krispens, William
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes. Weinberger was retained by the Workers' Defense Union to defend Krispens, an alien being held for deportation as an anarchist.
    - Correspondence
      - Biedenkapp, Fred (3), 1920 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Flynn, Elizabeth G.
        See: Workers' Defense Union, box 37, folder 8
      - Krispens, William (1), Undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - U.S. Supreme Court, Clerk (1), 1920 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Workers' Defense Union (4), 1920 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Legal papers, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Lachowsky, Hyman
    See: Abrams, Jacob, box 2, folder 1
  - Latson, William R. C.
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, scrapbook, and miscellaneous papers. When William Richard Cunningham Latson, author and an editor of Health Culture magazine, committed suicide, Weinberger took charge of the estate. This section contains letters to and from Latson before his death as well as Weinberger's correspondence with Latson's creditors, his publishers, and former associates. Also included are Weinberger's efforts to force the estranged husband of Latson's daughter to contribute to her support.
    - Correspondence
      - A-C, F, G, L-N, O-W (78), 1910-1914, 1916 (Box 37, Folder 10-11)
      - Alexander, Arthur A. (10), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Bleeker, Cornelia A. (6), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Brown, A.D. (2), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - The Gilbert Publishing Co. (8), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Goss, Gertrude A. (43), 1911-1916 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Goss, Walter W. (30), 1911-1915 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Health Culture
        See: Turner, Albert, box 37, folders 19-20
      - Latson, Gertrude (21), 1911-1915 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Lawton, Nathan O. (4), 1911-1912, 1915 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Library of Congress (4), 1912 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Lunsford, J. J. (4), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Mickle, W. H. (5), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Miller, Eugene M. (8), 1915 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - The Nautilus, 1908, 1910-1916 (Box 37, Folder 17-18)
      - Towne, Elizabeth
        See: The Nautilus, box 37, folders 17-18
      - Turner, Albert (67), 1910-1914 (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
      - Turner, H. W. (3), 1911 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Wolff, William A. (6), 19101-1911 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Legal papers, 1907, 1911, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Financial materials of Latson, 1910-1911 (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
    - Scrapbook belonging to William R. C. Latson, Undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Law, Jack
    See: St. John, Vincent, box 45, folder 17
  - Lipman, Samuel
    See: Abrams, Jacob box 2, folder 4
  - Mariani, Vito
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, and miscellaneous papers. Weinberger was retained by the Comitate Pro-Vittime Pelitiche to represent Mariani who was charged with criminal anarchy. As Mariani was a professed anarchist, Weinberger obtained a dismissal of the indictment against him and an order for immediate deportation to Italy.
    - Correspondence
      - Comitato Italiano Provittime Politiche (2), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Kovner, Hilda (2), 1921-1922 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Lega Italiana di Difesea Operaia (1), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Mariani, Nick (2), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Mariani, Nicola (1), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Mariani, Vito (25), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - New York American (1), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - New York Call (3), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - New York City District Attorney (10), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Ralston, Jackson H. (1), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (5), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Legal papers, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Notes (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Martin, Pedro
    See: Fernandez, Jose Ramon box 21, folder 15
  - Martinez, Thomas
    The papers consist of correspondence. Weinberger was retained by the American Civil Liberties Union to represent Martinez, an anarchist being held for deportation to Mexico. Weinberger succeeded in having Martinez freed on bail. He was later deported to Mexico.
    - American Civil Liberties Union (8), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Martinez, Thomas (24), 1919-1921 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Smith and Percy (1), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (48), 1920-1921 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Watson, Blanche (2), 1920 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Meirowitz, Irving
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes concerning New York vs. Irving Meirowitz, 1917. Meirowitz was arrested for disorderly conduct while making a speech. He had refused a policeman's order to stop speaking because the crowd was blocking traffic. He was fined $10. Weinberger appealed the decision.
    - Correspondence: Secular Society of New York (2), 1917 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Legal papers, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Notes (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Messinger, Joseph
    The papers consist of letters and legal papers New York vs. Joseph Messinger, 1916. Messinger was accused of having received stolen goods. Weinberger obtained an acquital.
    - Correspondence
      - Messinger, George (3), 1916 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - New York City Police Department (2), 1916 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Legal papers, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Micezer, Jose
    See: Fernandez, Jose Ramon box 21, folders 15-16
  - Mooney, Tom
    The papers consist of letters, notes, pamphlets, and miscellaneous papers. Weinberger did not act as an attorney for Tom Mooney, the labor organizer convicted and imprisoned for the San Francisco Preparedness Day bombing in 1916, but he did try to help secure a pardon for Mooney from the Governor of California. Weinberger was able to obtain a letter from one of the jurors in the Mooney trial requesting that Mooney be pardoned. One of Weinberger's clients, Alexander Berkman, was involved in the case. The San Francisco authorities tried to associate him with the Mooney case by charging him with murder. They failed in their attempt to extradite Berkman to California.
    - Correspondence
      - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (1), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - American Mercury (1), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Baker, Abby Scott (4) (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Johnston, Mercer G. (2), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Mish, Solomon (3), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Mooney, Rena (3), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Mooney, Tom (7), 1924-1925 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - The Nation (3), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - The New Republic (1), 1924 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Walsh, Frank P. (19), 1924-1925 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Tom Mooney trial and imprisonment
      Weinberger collected numerous pamphlets and booklets about the Mooney case and the controversy that it aroused. These materials are filed in this section.
      - Brief by C. M. Fickert, Undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1916, 1918-1919, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Pamphlet regarding law and order, by San Francisco Chamber of Commerce, 1916 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Pamphlets, 1917-1920, 1924, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 8-12)
      - Statements, 1916-1918, 1935, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Mosson, Isidore
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, and miscellaneous papers concerning Isidore Mosson vs. Jacob Sackett and Hyman Jacobs, 1926-1928. Mosson hired Weinberger to bring suit against the driver and the owner of a horse-drawn cart that damaged his automobile and injured him.
    - Correspondence
      - Brooklyn Manhattan Railroad Co. (1), 1927 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Globe Indemnity Co. (1), 1927 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Jacobs, H. (2), 1926 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Mosson, Isidore (4), 1926-1927 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - New York City Department of Licenses (4), 1926, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Price, Michael (1), 1926 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Reichman, Emil H. (2), 1928 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Schachne, Abraham (2), 1928 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Legal papers, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - New York Theatrical Press Agents
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, and miscellaneous papers. Weinberger was legal advisor to the newly formed New York Theatrical Press Agents.
    - Correspondence
      - Chisholm, Elise (2), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Henderson, Roy (2), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Michigan Circuit Court of Appeals (1), 1938 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - New York Theatrical Press Agents (17), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Weinberger, Milton R. (4), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Legal papers, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Notes, miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Newlander, Carl
    The papers consist of letters and legal papers concerning United States vs. Carl Newlander, 1918-1920. Weinberger represented Newlander, an anarchist, who was deported to his native Sweden.
    - Correspondence
      - Fitzgerald, Eleanor M.
        See: League for the Amnesty of Political Prisoners, box 40, folder 9
      - Kimmelman, Bessie (3), 1918 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - League for the Amnesty of Political Prisoners (4), 1918-1919, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Nelson, N. O. (1), 1918-1919, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Newlander, Carl (17), 1918-1920 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Harold Spielburg Agency (5), 1918-1919 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Sweden, Legation of (1), 1919 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Department of Justice (6), 1918-1920 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (15), 1918-1919 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Novikoff, Ivan
    See: Derkach, Alexander box 20, folder 12
  - O'Brian, Charles M.
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, and clippings concerning New York vs. Charles M. O'Brien, 1920-1923. Weinberger was attorney for O'Brien, charged with criminal anarchy and held for deportation to Canada. Weinberger was retained by the Proletarian Party of Rochester, New York.
    - Correspondence
      - Kelly, James W. (26), 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Nelles, Walter (3), 1921 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - New York City District Attorney (1), 1921 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - New York State, Monroe County District Attorney (18), 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - O'Brian, Charles M. (26), 1920-1923 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Proletarian Party, O'Brian Defense Committee (29), 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Recht, Charles (2), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (4), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - U.S. Department of State (1), 1921 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Legal papers, 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Notes, newspaper clippings, 1920-1922 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Oretissa, Elario
  - Orlick, David
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes concerning United States vs. David Orlick, 1919-1920. Orlick was charged, along with Lena Chenenky, Max Gendlin, and Morris Schneiderman, with being an anarchist and a member of the Communist Party. He was held for deportation, but the warrant was cancelled due to a lack of evidence.
    - Correspondence
      - Fleschler, A. (2), 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - Orlick, David (10), 1920, 1922 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (6), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Legal papers, 1920 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Notes (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Parsons, Robert
    The papers consist of letters and notes. Weinberger was attorney for Parsons, an alien held for deportation as an anarchist. Canada refused to admit Parsons, because he could not prove that he was a Canadian citizen. The United States Government contended that he was a Russian citizen, but, as Russia would not take deportees, he was released.
    - Correspondence
      - Bernstein, Rose (1), 1926 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Cohn, Michael A. (1), 1928 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Parsons, Michael A. (3), 1926 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Schwebel, Jacob (1), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 23)
      - Shorr, Isaac (6), 1926-1928 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (14), 1920, 1926-1928 (Box 40, Folder 24)
      - Wirin, A. L. (2), 1937 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Notes (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Pavlova, Pearl
    The papers consist of letters. Weinberger was retained by the Workers' Defense Union to try to have Pavlova's deportation warrant cancelled because of illness.
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (4), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Workers' Defense Union (1), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Perales, Pedro
    See: Rangel, Jesus M. box 43, folder 15
  - Perrone, Felipe (5), Undated (Box 40, Folder 27)
    The papers consist of letters. Weinberger was retained by the Workers' Defense Union in the deportation case of Perrone.
  - Perruchon, Peter
    The papers consist of letters. Perruchon was held as an anarchist in Leavenworth for about two years. Then Weinberger, retained by the American Civil Liberties Union, began deportation proceedings.
    - Kovner, Hilda (3), 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Perruchon, Peter (12), 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (16), 1919-1920 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Workers' Defense Union (1), 1920 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Potash, Irving
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, and notes. Potash, after serving eight months for criminal anarchy, was held for deportation. Weinberger, retained by the Workers' Defense Union, demonstrated that there were insufficient grounds for deportation.
    - Correspondence
      - American Civil Liberties Union (1), 1921 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Flynn, Elizabeth G.
        See: Workers' Defense Union, box 40, folder 29
      - Potash, Irving (13), 1920-1922 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - U.S. Department of Labor, Immigration (11), 1920-1921 (Box 40, Folder 29)
      - Workers' Defense Union (11), 1920-1922 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Legal papers, Undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Prober, Gabriel
    See: Abrams, Jacob box 1, folder 9 - box 3, folder 8
  - Provincetown Players
    The papers consist of letters, legal papers, notes, clippings, and miscellaneous papers concerning the Provincetown Players. Weinberger was attorney for the Provincetown Players, a pioneering group of theatrical artists that presented original works by American playwrights. The group is best known for presenting plays by Eugene O'Neill.
    - Correspondence
      - C, G, L-N, P, S, W (28), 1920, 1922-1924, 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Alsberg, H.G. (9), 1929-1930 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - The Bankers Industrial Exposition (1), 1929 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Bierne, Deborah (17), 1920-1921, 1928 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Cane, Melville H. (2), 1929 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Cook, George Cram (6), 1921, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Deeter, Jasper (1), 1921 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Fitzgerald, M. Eleanor
        See: The Provincetown Players, box 41, folder 9-10